M really doesn't mind you make a little extra money on the side, Dryden.
She just prefer if it wasn't sense secrets.
If this theatric is supposed to scare me, you have the wrong man, Bond.
If M was so sure I was bent, -
-she would have sent an 00.
As being section chief, I'd known if anyone had been permitted 00 status.
- Your file's showing no kills, but it takes ... - Two.
Shame. We barely got to know each other.
I know where you keep your gun.
So I've learned something.
True.
- How did he die? - Your contact? Not well.
Made you feel it, did it?
Well, you needn't worry, the second ...
Yes. Considerably.
007 STATUS CONFIRMED
So, how do I trust this man that I've never met with my money?
They ask for the introduction. That's all my organisation will garuantee.
I suppose our friend, Mr White.. that I've provided the bank services -
- for many other freedom fighters over the years.
- Do you believe in God, Mr. Le Chiffre? - No.
I believe in a reasonable rate of eternety.
- I want no risk on the portefolio. - Agreed.
- And I can access it anywhere in the world? - Yes.
I have the money, so sell my Skyfleet stock.
Sir, you must know you're betting against the market.
Noone expect these shares to go anywhere else but up.
Just do it.
Looks like our man. Burnt scare on his fist.
I wonder if bomb makers are insured against this.
He is on the move.
He's heading straight on me.
- Stop touching your ear.  - Sorry?
Put your hand down!
Toss that bloody weapon, I need him alive.
Listen to me.
Wheeping blood comes from a disarrangement of the lachrymal duct.
Nothing seriously.
I have two pairs, and you have a 17,4 % schance of making a Straight.
BRITISH GOVERNMENT AGENT KILLS UNARMED PRISONER
When does Ellipsis expire?
We have less than 36 hours ...
No, no, that's all the time I have in, mate.
Let our guests have 5 minutes to leave.
Or throw them overboard.
Who the hell do they think that they are?
Even the Prime Minister is smart enought to not ask questions about what we do.
Have you ever seed such a buch of self rightous ass covering frings?
They don't care what we do, they only care about what we get photographed doing.
And how the hell could Bond be so studpid?
I give him 00 status and he celebrates by shooting up an embassy.
And where the hell is he?
In the old days, when they did something that embarassing,they had the good sense to defect.
Christ, I miss the cold war.
- You got a bloody cheek. - Sorry.
- I'll shoot the camera next time. - Or yourself.
Yoy stormed into an embassy.
You violated the only absolute rule in international relationships.
And why? So you could kill a nobody.
We wanted to question him, not to kill him.
For God's sake, you're supposed to display a sense of judgement.
I did.
I thought to extinct a bombmaker would be a good thing.
One bombmaker.
We're trying to find out how an entire group of terrorists are financed, -
- and you give us one bombmaker.
The man isn't even a true believer.
He is a gun for hire.
And thanks to your over developed trigger finger we have no idea of who hired him or why.
- And where the hell did you find out where I lived? - Same way I found out your name.
- I had no idea what M stood for ... - Utter one more sylabelle and I'll have you killed.
I knew it was too early to promote you.
And I understand 00's have a very short life expectancy
So your mistake will be very short lived.
Bond, this is maybe too much for a blunt instrument to understand.
- but arrogance and self awareness seldom go hand in hand.
So you want me to be half munk and half hitman?
Any munk can kill. I want you to take your ego out of the equation.
And to judge the situation dispassionately.
I have to know if I can trust you.. and to know that you know who to trust.
Since I don't know that, I need you out of my sight.
Stick your head in the sand and think about your future.
Because these bastards want your head, -
- and I am seriously considering feeding you to them.
And Bond ...
Don't ever break into my house again.
Good day sir,  welcome to the Ocean Club.
Hello? Are you going to take this, or make me wait?
Sorry sir, sorry sir.
Welcome to the Ocean Club sir, checking in?
Yes.
It's a last moment, but do you have a room?
- We have an ocean view villa. - Perfect.
Could you do me a favour, I was at a dinner last night, and I parked my car next to a beautiful 1964 Aston Martin....
- and I'am ashamed to say that I nicked the door and..
Mr. Dimitrios.
If it isn't noticed, I'm not sure I would mention it.
But if I felt contempt to find him..
He has a house just up the beach.
Thank you.
- What? - He is in the Bahamas.
You want to share his holiday plans?
He is logged into our secure web site using your name and password.
How the hell does he know these things?
I'll do my best to find out.
- Who's he looking at? - Alex Dimitrios.
That slimy bugger.
No known associates.
Le Chiffre.
Have a good night club, gentlemen.
- What shall I serve? - Good evening. A vodka martini.
Sharp, big boy.
- Mind if I join you? - Good evening.
- Small blind. Big blind. - I'm in.
That's to you.
If that's for luck, you're twelve late.
- Left to you? - I heard you.
- Check or bet. - Check.
- And you? - 5000.
Five to call.
- Check. - Check to you, sir.
All in.
No, wait.
- 20.000. - Table sticks, I'm sorry sir.
This is on the table. that's my car. You'll bet?
Sorry, mr. Dimitrios.
Please, give him the chance to win his money back.
All right, show me, gentlemen.
Three kings.
Triple aces. Aces win.
Oh, and the valet ticket.
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you, sir.
No wonder he was such a phoney.
- My mistake. - Can I give you a lift home?
Oh that would really send him over the hills.
- I'm afraid I'm not that cruel. - Or you're just out of practice.
- Perhaps. - What about a drink at my place?
Your place? Is it close?
Very.
One drink.
- Good evening sir, and welcome back. - Welcome to my home.
I have a hard time seeing this is my fault. It's your plan, all I did was get you the man.
A man under surveillance by the British Secret Service.
- Which makes me wonder if I can trust you at all. - So don't, I couldn't care less.
But I do care about my reputation.
I have someone else for you to do the job.
He just needs the particulars. And payment.
You like married women, don't you James?
That keeps it simple.
What is it about bad men?
You.. my husband..
I have so many chances to be happy -
- so many nice guys.
Why can't nice guys be more like you?
They would be bad.
But so much more interresting.
What makes your husband a bad man?
His nature, I suppose.
- The nature of his work? - A mystery I'm afraid.
I'm also afraid you sleep with me in order to get to him.
- Are you afraid? - Not enough to stop.
Can I ask you a personal question?
No, won't seem like the properiate time.
Does Ellipsis mean anything to you?
- Should I ask him about it? - Perhaps later.
Yes, dear?
Ok, I understand. See you tomorrow, bye bye.
Apparently, he's on the last flight to Miami.
So you have all night to question me.
In that case we'll need more champagne.
- Good evening, room service. - Good evening.
Can I have a bottle of Bollinger, La Grand Annee -
- And Beluga caviar? - Yes, with everything.
- Would that be for two, sir? - What?
- No, for one.
Wait here.
Hello?
- Yes? - It's Bond.
- I need her now. - I'm afraid she can't be disturbed. Can I take a message?
Listen, you go and find her, tell her to call security at Miami airport , -
- because I think that a bomb is about to go off. Can you do it now?
I can put you on hold.
Bond? What the hell are you up to?
I call you back.
- A Skyfleet S570 prototype. - What about it?
Largest airplane in the world, to be revieled today at Miami airport.
Bond? Bond!
His target is the Skyfleet prototype. It's launching today.
I got to go.
The poll's expired. I'm sorry, I'm not sure how much you've lost
101.206.000 dollars.
Quite a body pile you're stacking up.
She was tortured first...
... as you already killed her husband, she must have been the only one left to question.
- Did she know anyhting compromising? - No.
- Your name, what you're after? - No.
Dimitrios was the middle man, he knew how to put his hands on weapon, and people to use them.
Hw worked for anyone who had money.
He was involved with a man called Le Chiffre, -
- a private banker for the world's terrorists.
He invested their money and gave them access to it wherever they want it.
Og good, you're here.
Albanian we believe, chess protegy, mathematical genious, likes to show it by playing poker.
- So you can keep an eye on me? - Yes.
When they analyzed the stock market up to 9.11, -
- the CIA discovered a massive shortage of airline stocks.
When the stock hit the bottom on 9.11, somebody made a fortune.
The same thing happened this morning with Skyfleet stock, or was supposed to.
With their prototype destroyed, the company would have been a bancrupcy.
Instead, somebody lost over 100 million dollars betting the wrong way.
You think this man was Le Chiffre?
Which would explain how he could set up a high stakes poker game at Casino Royale in Montenegro.
10 players, $10 million buy in, $5 millioner re-buy
Winner takes all, potentially $150 millions.
Good, then we know where he'll be. Do you want a clean kill or do you want to send a message?
We want him alive. Le Chiffre doesn't have a $100 million to loose.
He played the stock market with his client's funds?
They won't be too happy when they find out it's gone.
We can't let him win this game. If he looses, he has nowhere to run.
We'll give him sanfry in return for everything he knows.
I'm putting you in the game. Replacing someone playing for a syndicate.
According to Villiers, you are the best player in the Service.
Thust me, I wish it wasn't the case.
I would ask you if you could remain emotionally detached.
- But I know that's not your problem, is it Boond? - No.
Don't worry about keeping in touch. We know where you are.
You can stop pretending.  You knew I wouldn't let it stop, didn't you?
When I knew you were you.
I am the money.
Every penny of it.
The treasury has agreed to stake you in the game.
Vesper. I hope your parent had it for that.
Thank you.
You must be well connected, I've never seen so much be done so quickly.
Or so stylishly.
- May I ask you where it is? - $10 millions was wired to your account in Montenegro.
With contuingency for 5 more, if I deem it a good looking investment.
I suppose you've given some thought to to the notion that if you loose, -
- our government would have directly financed terrorism.
So you're telling me it's a matter of probability?
I was worried it was some chance involved.
You'll never see the player with the best hand win.
So that'll be what you call bluffing.
You've heard the term?
Then you'll know that in poker you never play your hand, but the man a across from you.
- And you are good at reading people? - Yes, I am.
Which is why I've noticed an undertone of sarcasm in your voice.
-
- You don't think this is a very good plan, do you? - So there is a plan?
I got the impression we were risking millions of dollars and houndreds of lives in a game of luck.
- What else can you advice, mr. Bond? - About you, miss Lynd?
Well, your beauty is a problem.
You worry you're not being taken seriously.
Which is what you can say of any effective woman with a heart and brain.
True, but this one overcompensates by wearing slugging masculine clothing -
- and being more aggresive than her female collegues.
And ironically enough, and makses it less likely for her to be accepted and promoted by her male superiors, -
- and mistake it a curtesy for arrogance.
Now I'd normally go with "only child", but -
- I would go for "Orphan".
All right.
By the cut of your suit you went to Oxford, -
- naturally thinking that human beings are dressed like that, but you worried it was demanded.
My guess is that you didn't come from money, and your school friends never let you forget it.
Which means that you were at that school by the grace of someone else's charity.
And since you first thought of me being as an orphan, I would say that you are.
And you are? I like this poker thing.
And that makes perfect sense, -
- since MI6 looks for an adjusted young man who gives little though to sacrificing others in order to protect queen and country.
You know, former SAS types with easy smiles and expensive watches.
- Rolex? - Omega.
Beautiful.
Now, after having first met you, I wouldn't go as far as calling you a cold hearted bastard.
But it wouldn't be a stretch to imagine -
- that you think of women as disposable pleasures, rather feminine pursuits.
So as charming as you are, mr. Bond, I will be keeping an eye of our government's money -
- and off of your perfectly formed ass.
- You noticed? - Even accountants have imagination.
- How was your lamb? - Stewed, my symphatys.
- Good evening, mr. Bond. - Good evening, miss Lynd.
- Hotel Splendide, sir? - That's right.
- Thank you, sir. - Thank you.
It's last minutes details.
Apparently, we're very much in love.
- Do you usually leave it to the porter to tell you this sort of things? - Only when it's a necessary brief.
I am mr. Arlington Beach, a professional gambler.
And you are miss Stephanie Broadchest...
- You have to trust me on this. - You know I don't.
We've been involved quite awhile, hence the shared suite.
But my familiy is strict roman catholic, therefore for prudence's sake it will be a due two bedroom suite.
I do hate it, when religion comes between us.
Religion and a securely locked door.
- Am I going to have a problem with you, Bond? - No, don't worry, you'rfe not my type.
- Smart? - Single.
- Welcome to the Hotel Splendide, what is your name, sir. - James Bond. You'll find the reservation under "Beach".
- Welcome, mr. Bond. - You sign right there, you represent the treasury.
- Thank you, enjoy your stay. - I will.
Very funny.
Look, Le Chiffre know I'm well connected, he also knows who I am and where the money is coming from.
Which means he has decided to play me anyway.
He is either desperate or he is overly confident,  He is either desperate or overly self confident. But either way, that tells me something about him.
And all he gets in return is a name that he already has.
You know he knows something about you. He knows you are reckless.
Take the next one. It isn't room enough for me and your ego.
- Mr. Bond, this is for you. - Thank you.
I love you too, M.
My name is Mathis. Rene Mathis. I am your contact here.
- Does he know we have been watching him? - Le Chiffre? I don't think so.
Probably because there is no "we". Just me.
I'm afraid if you get into trouble here, recovery won't come over the next hill.
Le Chiffre arrived yesterday.
I've spent the time reestablishing old relationships.
The cief of police is here now, very close.
It is him, with the mustache, over my left shoulder.
- That can make life quite difficult. - And quite possible shorter.
He is not a very subtile man.
I thought about buying his services, but -
- but quite franky, I couldn't afford to outbid Le Chiffre.
I hate to say it, but the accountants seem to be running MI6 these days.
Not that I have anything against accauntants.
Many of them are lovely.
So I decided it was cheeper to supply his deputy with evidents -
- that we were bribing the chief.
It's amazing what we can do with Photoshop these days, isn't it.
I think your odds are improving, mr Bond.
- Yes? - For you.
Something you expect med to wear?
I need you to look fabulous, -
- so when you walk up behind me and kiss me on my neck, the players will think about your neckline and not their cards.
Do you think you can do that for me?
I'll do my best.
Thank you.
- I have a dinner jacket. - There are dinner jackets and there are dinner jackets.
This is the latter, and I need you looking like a man who belongs at that table.
How...
- It is tailored. - I sliced you up when we met.
- Good evening, sir. - Good evening.
Thank you.
Then you must be mr. Bliss' replacement. Welcome, mr. Beach.
Or is that Bond? I am a little confused.
Oh, we wouldn't want that, would we?
Monsieur Mendel. Please sit down.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome.
As you know, the game is "no limit", Hold'em poker. Five communual cards and two on the hold.
Monsieur Mendel represents the Basel banks in Switzerland holding the sticks.
Mesdames et messieurs. You have each deposited $10 millions buy in.
Further buy in of $5 million can be made by electronic transfer.
The money will remain in ascrow until the winner enters his password into the encrypter.
Whereupon the entire sum will be wired to any bank account in the world you nominate.
Mr. Bond?
We proceed alphabetically. Please be so kind as to enter a password of your choice.
Six letters or more.
High card from dealer position.
Monsieur Gallardo, mr. Kaminoksky has a small blind for $5000, -
- and mr. Fukutu the big blind for $10.000.
Enjoy the game.
Four players.
Your bet?
Check. Check.
Bet $50.000.
Call.
Fold.
Fold. Heads-up.
Monsieur Le Chiffre?
Bet $100.000.
- You were supposed to enter so the others could see you. - Was I? Forgive me.
Good luck darling.
It's up to you, monsieur Bond.
- Monsieur Bond? - Excuse me, what was the bet? $100.000?
Call.
I suppose I don't have to tell you how beautiful you look?
Half the people at that table are still watching you.
Champagne.
Monsieur Le Chiffre?
Bet $200.000.
Monsieur, you have been called. Show your cards please.
Full house to monsieur Le Chiffre. 9's over 2's.
Mr. Bond?
Fold.
Send the barman over, please.
Dry Martini. Wait.
Three measures of Gordon's, one of vodka, half a measure of China Lillet. Shake up, add some ice and a thin slice of lemon.
- Yes, sir. - Bruno, I'll have one of those.
- So will I. - Certainly.
Fred, bring me one as well, and keep the fruit.
That's it?
- Anyone wants play poker now? - One's in a hurry.
Will you excuse me.
- Taste nice - I thought we dispenced the covers.
No, we dispenced with one that was of no use and created another that is.
- Is he watching? - Yes.
This is mean character, pissed off because you're loosing so fast we won't be here past midnight.
I'll bring my character's feelings mirror my own.
You know that's not half bad. I must come up with a name for that.
He was worth it. To discover his talent.
- What do you mean? - The twich he has to hide when he bluffs.
- Bluffs? He had the best hand. - Which he got on the last card.
The odds against was 23 to 1 and he knew that.
When he did his first raise he had nothing.
Then it was blind luck. You got the bug?
Yes.
Thank you.
Maybe he can fix his deposit half.
Ladies and gentlemen. Mesdames et messieurs. We have now been playing for 4 hours.
It's time for a short break. We will resume play in one hour.
Well, I think I will report about the evenings "florentines".
- Sir. - You wanted to do what to me?
- You've lost me completely. - You said you couldn't wait to have me back in the room. Come on.
So what's so damned important?
I'm so..
Where is my money?
- Good evening. - You're holding a parcel for me?
Thank you.
You think you can loose that kind of money and no one will notice?
You money is safe.
Open that.
You'll have it tomorrow. All of it.
I will take a hand for this treason, but you need to use yours.
Hold out your arm.
Hold out your arm, my beaty.
Or I'll take your head.
Go to the room. Wait for me there.
Stairs.
Not a world of protest.
Should find a new boyfriend.
Go find Mathis, tell him I've hidden the bodies down here, and I want him to get rid of them.
Do that now. Go. Go!
You've changed your shirt, mr. Bond.
I hope our game doesn't make you transpire?
A little, but I don't consider myself in trouble until I start wheeping blood.
Ladies and gentlemen, if everybody's ready, let's continue the game.
The blood on my hands are not coming off.
May I see.
That's better?
- Cold? - Yes.
- Any trouble with the bodies? - Not at all.
Being dead doesn't mean one still can't be helpful.
Le Chiffre will keep looking over his shoulder, wondering who it will come from next.
How is our girl?
Melted your cold heart?
- Fold. - Fold.
And fold.
Three players.
- Monsieur? - 300 grand.
Bet, $300.000.
Call.
And call.
Three players.
Check.
Monsieur Bond?
Bet $500.000.
Look, its the tank, he's bluffing.
My God, James was right.
It's up to you.
Raise, $1 million.
Seem someone know something I don't.
Fold. Heads-up, gentlemen.
It's up to you.
Two.
Will raise, $2 million.
It's up to you.
I'm all in.
Well it's $14,5 millioner. It is up to you, monsieur Bond.
Bond will have to call all in to call his bluff.
- Call. - Call.
Gentlemen, showdown, please.
Full house, kings and aces.
Monsieur Le Chiffre?
It's four checks. Monsieur Le Chiffre wins.
You thought I was bluffing, mr. Bond.
Please, we now break for one hour.
When we return, big blind will be $200.000.
I'm gonna need the other $5 million to buy me back in.
I can't do that, James.
Look, I made a mistake.
I was impatient, maybe I was arrogant, but I can beat him.
- I'm sorry - Sorry? Sorry?
Why aren't you putting that in a sentence, like maybe, "sorry that Le Chiffre wins, -
- continuing terrorism and killing innocent people."
You lost because of your ego. And your ego can't take it.
- All you're going to do now is loose more. - Well then you're an idiot.
- I'm sorry? - I said you're a bloody idiot.
Look in my eyes.
I can beat this man. You know that.
Put your hand off my arm.
- Vodka Martini. - Shaken or stirred?
Do I look like I give a damn?
- James, get the girl.
Sorry, I should introduce myself since we seem related.
Felix Leiter. A brother from Langley.
You shall have a little faith. You keep your head above you, I think you have him.
Had. Excuse me.
- You're not buying in? - No.
Listen, I'm bleeding chips. I'm not gonna last much longer.
You have a better chance, I'll stake you.
I'm saying I'll give you the money to keep going.
Just one thing. If it bought off, the CIA brings him in.
And what about the winnings?
Does it look like we need the money?
Shall we up the blinds?
Why not.
Bet.
Rise.
Excuse me.
- Call. - Rise $500.000.
- Fold. - Thank you.
Fold.
- Give me. - Sorry sir, you are big blind.
- Who is it? - 007.
Bond's being poisened. He's going into a cardiac arrest.
Stay calm, don't interrupt, you will be dead within two minutes uness you do exactly like I tell you.
- I'm all ears. - Remove the defillibrator from the couch.
- Do we know what it is yet? - We're still scanning.
Attach the leads to your chest.
Ventricular takykardi - digitalis. What did they give him?
- As soon as it reads charged ... the button ... - Don't push the red button!
- You hear me, don't push it yet. - His heart's gonna stop.
There is time for only one charge.
Take the blue combi pen, Bond. Mid neck. Into the vein.
You will pass out in a few seconds, push the red button now, Bond!
- Bond, push the red button. - Do it now!
- You ok? - Me?
- Thank you. - You're welcome. Take a trip to the hospital.
I'll do.
- Soon as I've won this game - You're not seriously going back there.
I wouldn't dream of it.
Bet $1 million.
- All in. - Gentllemen, showdown please.
To pair. Aces and sevens
Queen plays. Wins.
I'm sorry,  The last hand almost killed me.
Gentlemen, with this chip exchange we enter the final phase of the game. There's no more buyings.
The big blind is now $1 million dollars.
Four players.
It's your bet.
- Monsieur Bond? - Check.
$24 million in the pot already.
- Check. - Check. All check.
Four players.
- Check. - Check.
All in. $6 million.
Bet. $6 millioner. All in.
$5 million. All in.
Bid is $6 million.
Rise.
Rise $12 million.
Heads-up.
$40,5 millioner. All in.
Rise. All in.
Well, I think I will call your lepard.
Call.
$150 millioner in the pot.
Gentlemen, showdown please.
Flush. Ace, king, queen.
Full house. Eights and aces.
Higher full house..
Aces and six'es.
Monsieur Bond?
5 and 7 of spades.
Straight Flush. 4 till 8.
A high hand.
Monsieur Bond wins.
- Please. - Thank you very much.
- He is all yours. - I appreciate it, brother.
Congratulations.
- You know it is no celebration in it. - You were almost dead an hour ago.
Come on, I'm finished.
Mathis says the americans have contacted Le Chiffre.
They think to extract him before dawn.
You know, I think I would call that a Vesper.
- Is it the after taste? - No.
Because once you have tasted it, that's all you want to cook.
- That was quite a good line. - That's a very good line.
- But you're laughing at it. - Not so much because of you.
Well, that's fine.
I'll figure out what that is.
- It's an algerian love knot. - Really?
- I thought it was just pretty. - No.
Someone gave it to you.
He is a very lucky man.
You can switch off so easily, can't you?
Doesn't bother you killing these people?
I wouldn't be much if I did.
I don't believe you.
You got a choice you know.
Just because you've done something, doesn't mean you keep doing it.
Why is it people who can't take advice also insist giving it?
Are you thinking I don't take my own advice?
I think something is driving you.
And I think I'll never find out what it is.
Mathis needs me.
Good night. Congratulations again.
Mathis.
I'm afraid your friend Mathis, is really ... my friend.
Bond ...
You've taken good care about your body.
Such a vaste.
You know, I've never understood these levelled tortures.
It's the simplest things -
-to cause more pain than a man can possibly enjoy.
And of course, it's not only the immediate pain, but the knowledge that if you don't give up quickly enough-
- there will be not much left to define you as a man.
The only question remains...
Will you give up in time?
I want the money.
Miss Lynd will give me the account number, if she has not already.
So all I need from you is the password.
The password.. please.
I've gotten an itch.. down there.
Would you mind?
No! No!
To the right, to the right, to the right.
You are a funny man, mr. Bond.
Yes, yes, yes!
Now the whole world's gonna know that you died while scratching my balls.
I died? I died ...?
Yes, because no matter what you do, I'm not gonna give you the password -
- which means that your clients will hunt you down and cut you in little pieces of meat while you're still breathing.
Because if you kill me, there will be nowhere else to hide.
But you are so wrong!
Because after I've slaughted you and your little girlfriend-
- your people will still welcome me with open arms.
Give me the password.
And I will at least let her live.
Do it soon enough, she will still be in one peace.
- You really arn't going to tell me? - No.
So I think ... -
- I will feed you with what you have undone.
I'll get the money.
Tell them, I'll get the money.
Money isn't as valuable to our organisation as the ability to trust.
Any ideas?
- What? - Why he left the two of you alive.
Where is she?
Sleeping.
And I'm supposed to make you drink this.
It's just odd.
Killing all, but leaving you and her untouched.
Almost like someone tried to tell us something.
Did you look at the killer?
No.
Shame.
Drink up.
Anything else you remember?
- Anything else that can help us? - Help us?
Or help you?
- Hello. - Hello.
You're all right?
I came just to waking you.
You're always looking at me like you haven't seen me in years.
Makes me feel reborn.
If you've just been born -
- would you be naked?
You have me there.
You can have me anyway.
I can?
Yes, here, there, any way you like.
- Does this mean that you will make love to me? - Yes, that's how I would describe it.
Not long ago, if you described your feeling about me not long ago..
..I'm trying to find a better word than "nobody".
I'm afraid I'm a complicated woman.
That's something to be afraid of.
Hello.
Perfect timing.
Mr. Mendel, how are things in Switzerland?
My apologies. I do not mean to rush, but a $120 million is a large sum of money.
It certainly is. You didn't bring anyt chocolate with you?
I'm afraid not.
If you would type in the account number,
- And then the password - You can do that.
I would if I knew what it was.
V ... E ... S ... P ... E ... R.
The account has been transferred. Sorry to disturbing you.
- Auf wiedersehen. - Auf wiedersehen.
You know, James?
I just want you to know that if all that was left of you... -
- was your smile and your little finger ...
you would be more of a man than anyone else.
That's because you know what I can do with my little finger.
- I have no idea. - But you're aching to find out..
You're not going to let me in there?
You got your armor back on.
I have no armor left.
You stripped it from me.
What there is left of me.
Whatever is left of me..
Whatever I am..
I'm yours.
M won't miss me for a couple of days.
- She'll be too busy sweating Mathis. - Mathis?
Remember, what I told you about Le Chiffre, Mathis told Le Chiffre.
That's how he won me out.
The same goes for the implant, I'm not going to miss that.
- I can't believe that. - Neither could I.
I thougth he hid my back.
But there you go.
Does everyone have a toll?
Yes.
Yes, everyone.
Everyone except you.
That's why I love you.
Do you love me?
Enough to float around the world with you, until one of us must find an honest job.
But I think that's gonna be you, because I have no idea what an honest job is.
Are you serious?
Like you said ...
If you do what I do for too long, then there'll not be any soul left to salvage.
I'm leaving with all that I have left.
Is that enough for you?
No stop, I've gotta go to the bank.
What's the time?
How much do you think we need to float for a month?
I got plenty.
I want to pay for my half.
You stopped wearing your necklace.
Yes. It was time.
Time enough to look after the soul?
You realize that one cannot always forget the past.
Apparently not for your employer.
Back in one month.
Come on, I get money, you get supplies.
Be back here in half an hour.
- Hello, M. - I got your note.
- Yes? - We'll talk about that later.
Right now I have a man from treasury here.
He wonders if you ever is going to deposit the winnings.
That's a shame, I didn't think they'd miss it.
Yes. I told them not to worry.
- So you'll deposit today? - I'm on my way to the bank right now.
James Bond for mr. Mendel.
Mr Mendel, I have some trouble accessing the funds of my account.
It was transferred to the bank account number your company gave us, mr Bond.
It appears the money is being drawn as we speak.
Where?
The Venece branch of course, at St. Mark's Square.
Is there a problem, mr. Bond?
- I'll kill her! - Allow me.
I'm sorry, James.
She had a boy friend, a French Algerian.
They were vey much in love.
He was kidnapped by the organisation behind Le Chiffre.
And they blackmailed her and wanted to kill him, unless she cooperated.
We should have picked up on it, but sometimes we're so focused on our enemies, we forget to watch our friends.
How are you doing?
She left her cell phone.
She must have known I'd check it.
She knew you were you.
- Well, at least this clears Mathis. - No.
- No? - No, it just proves that he's guilty, not innocent.
Could be a double blind.
- You don't trust anyone, do you, James? - No.
Then you've learned your lesson.
Come back as soon as you can, we need you.
Will do.
- If you do need time ... - Why should I need more time?
Job's done.
The bitch is dead.
James?
Did you ever asked yourself, why you weren't killed that night?
Isn't that obvious? She made a deal to spare your life in exchange for the money.
She hoped they would let her live.
But she must have known, she had to have her death.
And now we'll never know who was behind this.
The trail's gone cold.
- Hello? - Mr. White? We need to talk.
Who is this?
The name is Bond. James Bond.